Luther-Bagby collection, Inclusive: 1821-2001, Bulk: 1890-1970
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Smith Papers, 1887-1976; 3; 62 document boxes, 2 oversized boxes, and 3 oversized folders.
  - Financial Documents, 1914-1973; 3
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1943, 1961-1969, undated (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, circa 1943-1969, undated (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1945-1946, 1961-1968, undated (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1947-1959, undated (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, circa 1947-1973, undated (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1949-1951, undated (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1949-1950, 1958, 1961, undated (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1949, 1957, 1961, undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1950-1953, 1965-1966, undated (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, circa 1950-1966, undated (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, circa 1954-1961, undated (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, circa 1955-1965, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1956-1967, undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1957-1961, undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1958-1965, undated (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1959-1963, 1967, undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1960-1967, undated (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Statements, 1962-1966, undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1914-1922, 1952-1963, undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1918-1919, 1922-1924, undated (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1920-1922, 1967 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1922-1923, 1927, 1962-1972, undated (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1925-1926, 1931-1932 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1925-1926, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Personal Expenditures, circa 1927-1968, undated (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1930-1931, 1953-1957, 1963, undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1932-1933, 1940, 1965-1969, undated (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1934-1939, 1945-1947, 1949 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1934-1940, 1949 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Personal Expenditures, circa 1936-1951, undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Personal Expenditures: (1 of 2), circa 1938-1967, undated (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Personal Expenditures: (2 of 2), circa 1938-1967, undated (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Personal Expenditures, circa 1939-1958, undated (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Personal Expenditures, circa 1939-1967, undated (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Personal Expenditures: (1 of 2), circa 1940-1965, undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Personal Expenditures: (2 of 2), circa 1940-1965, undated (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Personal Expenditures, circa 1941-1954, undated (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Personal Expenditures, circa 1941-1965, undated (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1942, 1958, 1960-1965, undated (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Personal Expenditures, circa 1944-1969, undated (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1945, 1962-1969, undated (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Personal Expenditures, circa 1948-1969, undated (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1950, 1966, undated (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1950, 1967, undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1955-1957 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Personal Expenditures, circa 1958-1972, undated (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1959-1965, undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Personal Expenditures: (1 of 2), 1961 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Personal Expenditures: (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Personal Expenditures: (1 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Personal Expenditures: (2 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1961; 1964 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1962-1964 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1963-1965 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1963, 1971-1972, undated (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1964-1967 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Personal Expenditures: (1 of 2), 1965-1966, undated (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Personal Expenditures: (2 of 2), 1965-1966, undated (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1965-1967 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1966, undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1966-1967, undated (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Personal Expenditures, 1971-1973, undated (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - General, circa 1938-1965, undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - General, circa 1938-1969, undated (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - General, circa 1939-1967, undated (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - General, circa 1941-1969, undated (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - General, circa 1942-1964, undated (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Legal Documents, 1934-1973; 4
    This subseries consists of one folder of legal documents related to the Smith family, including land deed information, insurance documentation, and oil, gas, and mineral leases.
    - General, circa 1934-1973 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Literary Productions, 1912-2001; 4; 19 document boxes and 9 folders of oversized materials.
  This series contains 19 boxes of published and unpublished literary productions including subseries about schools, churches, periodicals, biographical materials, and general productions. The materials in this series were not included in the literary productions subseries of other series because the items did not distinctly relate to only one family represented in the collection. The first two subseries, schools and churches, both include material about institutions in the United States that members of the Luther-Bagby families visited or attended, as well as schools and churches in Brazil that the families were instrumental in founding as part of their mission work.
  - Schools, 1915-1973; 1
    This subseries contains materials about various schools in Brazil and the United States. The school most represented in the subseries is Colégio Batista, which was founded in 1926 in Porto Alegre by Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith. Materials about Baylor University and what is now the University of Mary Hardin-Baylor are also included in this subseries.
    - General, 1924-1926 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - General, 1927, 1953-1954, undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Colégio Batista (Porto Alegre): General, circa 1926-1970, undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Colégio Batista (Porto Alegre): General, circa 1932-1970, undated (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Colégio Batista (Porto Alegre): Bulletins, 1928, 1938, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Colégio Batista (Porto Alegre): Graduation Programs, 1939-1952 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Colégio Batista (Porto Alegre): Graduation Programs, 1954-1960 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Colégio Batista (Porto Alegre): Graduation Programs, 1961-1967 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Colégio Batista (Porto Alegre): Graduation Programs, 1968-1972 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Colégio Batista (Porto Alegre): Programs and Invitations, circa 1938-1972, undated (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Colégio Batista (Porto Alegre): Statutes and Regulations, 1969, undated (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Colégio Batista (Porto Alegre): Clippings, circa 1935-1966, undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Colégio Batista (Porto Alegre): El Instituto Biblico Ucranio al Rev. Dr. Guillermo Cooper, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Colégio Americano Baptista, 1927, undated (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Collegio Baptista (São Paulo): O Cruzeiro, 1933 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Collegio Baptista (São Paulo): O Cruzeiro, 1935 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Colégio Batista Brasileiro (São Paulo): Yearbook, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Colégio Batista Brasileiro (São Paulo): Yearbook, 1951 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Collegio Progresso Brazileiro, 1922 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Seminario Teologico Batista do Norte do Brasil, 1927-1928 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Seminario Teologico Batista do Norte do Brasil, 1939, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Seminario Teologico Batista do Sul do Brasil, 1937 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Southern Baptist Seminary, 1922, 1950 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Baylor College for Women and Mary Hardin-Baylor College [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor]: General, circa 1920-1973, undated (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Baylor College for Women [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor]: Blue Bonnet, 1919 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Baylor College for Women [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor]: Blue Bonnet, 1920 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Baylor College for Women [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor]: Blue Bonnet, 1921 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Baylor Female College [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor]: Quadrennial Baylorian, 1915-1916 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Mary Hardin-Baylor College [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor]: Centennial Materials, 1945 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Baylor Female College, Baylor College for Women, and Mary Hardin-Baylor College [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor]: Pamphlets and Booklets, circa 1907-1973, undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Mary Hardin-Baylor College [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor University]: Clippings, circa 1945-1969, undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Student Materials, circa 1929-1967, undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Student Materials: (1 of 2), undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Student Materials: (2 of 2), undated (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Teaching Materials: General, circa 1930-1964, undated (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Teaching Materials: English Pupils, circa 1950-1954, undated (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Churches, 1922-1973; 2
    This subseries largely consists of literary productions such as roll books, membership materials, and publications related to Igreja Batista Central, a Baptist church founded by Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith in Porto Alegre. There is also some literary productions from Columbus Avenue Baptist Church in Waco, Texas.
    - Igreja Batista Central: Membership Materials, circa 1922-1942, undated (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Membership Materials, circa 1940-1960, undated (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Membership Materials, circa 1940-1970, undated (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Membership Materials, circa 1942-1964, undated (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Membership Materials, circa 1943-1968, undated (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Membership Materials, 1954-1955 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Membership Materials, 1957-1958, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Fellowship Groups: Sociedade de Senhoras, circa 1927-1942, undated (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Fellowship Groups: Sociedade de Senhoras, circa 1935-1947, undated (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Fellowship Groups, circa 1928-1938, undated (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Roll Books, circa 1935-1951, undated (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Roll Books, 1947 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Objectives and Officer Responsibilities, undated (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Church Publications and Reports, circa 1941-1963, undated (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Comissao Central, circa 1944-1968, undated (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Igreja Batista Central: Clippings, circa 1945-1964, undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Igreja Batista Central: General, circa 1934-1963, undated (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Igreja Batista Central: General, circa 1941-1966, undated (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Igreja Batista Central: General, circa 1950-1962, undated (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Junta Estadoal Baptista, undated (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Columbus Avenue Baptist Church, 1969-1973, undated (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Periodicals, 1924-1973; 3
    The periodicals in this subseries address topics such as religion, mission work, and life in Brazil. The existing organization of the periodicals was maintained, with the general portion in alphabetical order and then the titles with more volumes also in alphabetical order.
    - General: A: (1 of 2), 1965, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - General: A: (2 of 2), 1965, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - General: B, 1927-1950, 1959-1960, 1970 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - General: B, 1924-1925,1951-1954, 1963-1967 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - General: B, 1925, 1931-1945, 1953-1967 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - General: C, 1942, 1944, 1953, 1962, 1966-1967 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - General: C-E, 1939-1967, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - General: F-H, 1935-1936, 1945-1955, 1960, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - General: I-M, 1932-1941, 1952-1955, 1960-1967, undated (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - General: N-P, 1933-1946, 1951-1952, 1959-1970, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - General: P, 1939, 1951-1955, 1965-1969, undated (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - General: R-T, 1940, 1946-1956, 1962-1969, undated (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - General: T, 1957, 1967 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - General: U-W, 1933, 1955-1958, 1962-1966 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - "A Vozclo Colegio Batista", 1950-1952, 1956-1957, 1960 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - "Batista Gaucho", 1947-1952 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - "Batista Gaucho", 1954, 1957-1961, 1965, 1968-1971 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - "Baptist Standard", 1927, 1934, 1950, 1955-1956 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - "Baptist Standard", 1956-1957, 1961, 1966-1967, 1970, undated (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - "Exortador", 1933-1934 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - "Exortador", 1934-1935, 1951-1955, 1958 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - "Exortador", 1941-1949 (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - "NOW", 1944, 1949-1952, 1958-1969 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - "O Presbiteriano Biblico", 1964-1967 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - "Southwestern News", 1944, 1951, 1958-1962 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - "Southwestern News", 1963-1967, 1971 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - "O Jornal Baptista" ["O Jornal Batista"], 1922, 1933, 1937 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - "O Jornal Baptista" ["O Jornal Batista"], 1928 (Box 125 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - "O Jornal Baptista" ["O Jornal Batista"], 1941-1971 (Box 126 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - "O Jornal Batista", 1940, 1954, 1960 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Biographical Materials, 1914-2001; 4
    This small subseries contains biographical materials that are associated with the Luther, Bagby, and Smith families as a whole and do not fit as well into any single family series. For additional biographical materials, see the literary production subseries of the first three series (I: Luther Papers, II: Bagby Papers, III: Smith Papers).
    - Family Tree, 1914, undated (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Funeral of Everett Gill, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Personal Rememberances, 1934-1948, 1962-1968, 2001 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Published and Unpublished Materials, 1914-1983; 5
    This subseries includes published and unpublished materials on religion, travel, and general topics. There are also several boxes of books at the end of this subseries that were collected by the Luther-Bagby family and provide an representative sampling of the type of books they owned.
    - General, circa 1916-1983, undated (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - General, circa 1925-1942, undated (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - General, circa 1927-1960, undated (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - General, circa 1936-1969, undated (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - General, 1967-1968, undated (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - General, 1967-1972, undated (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - General, undated (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1898-1919, undated (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1913, undated (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1929-1962, undated (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1931-1967, undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1933, undated (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1933-1963, undated (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1935-1964, undated (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1936, undated (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1936-1975, undated (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1939-1947, undated (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1940-1953, undated (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1944-1952, undated (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1946-1947, undated (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1947, undated (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1947-1957, undated (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1952-1965, undated (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1954-1961, undated (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Religious Documents: General, 1965-1967, undated (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Religious Documents: General, circa 1966-1968, undated (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Religious Documents: General: (1 of 3), undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Religious Documents: General: (2 of 3), undated (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Religious Documents: General: (3 of 3), undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Religious Documents: 10th Congress of Baptist World Alliance, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Religious Documents: One Hundred Years of Blood, Sweat, Joy and Tears, 1982 (Box 127 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Religious Documents: Catholicism, circa 1923-1949 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Religious Documents: Catholicism, 1966, undated (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Religious Documents: Catholicism, undated (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Religious Documents: Junta de Beneficencia, 1939-1954 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Religious Documents: Missoes Estaduais, 1963-1966 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Religious Documents: Missoes Estrangeiras, circa 1935-1947, undated (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Religious Documents: Missoes Nacionais, circa 1959-1966, undated (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Travel, 1914-1923, undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Travel, 1922-1936, undated (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Travel, 1940-1944, undated (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Travel, 1940-1952, undated (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Travel, 1953, undated (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Books, 1916, 1922 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Books, 1922, undated (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Books, 1924-1925, 1929 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Books, 1927 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Books: (1 of 3), undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Books: (2 of 3), undated (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Books: (3 of 3), undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Books: "Thirty-Six Years of Cottage Home History", 1928 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Books: "A Centennial History of the Baptist Women of Texas", 1933 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - "Southern Baptist Handbook", 1931 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Books: "Southern Baptist Annual", 1931 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Books: "Southern Baptist Annual", 1932 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Books: "Historia dos Batistas do Brasil", 1940 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Books: "Baptist Fundamentals", undated (Folder 5)
  - General, 1912-1977; 6
    This subseries contains clippings, information about clubs and organizations, programs and tickets, and other small sub-subseries of literary productions. Much of the material in this subseries is undated.
    - Clippings: Written in Porto Alegre: (1 of 4), 1924-1973, undated (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Clippings: Written in Porto Alegre: (2 of 4), 1924-1973, undated (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Clippings: Written in Porto Alegre: (3 of 4), 1924-1973, undated (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Clippings: Written in Porto Alegre: (4 of 4), 1924-1973, undated (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Clippings: William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (1 of 2), 1912-1959, undated (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Clippings: William Buck Bagby and Anne Luther Bagby: (2 of 2), 1912-1959, undated (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Clippings: Sidney McFarland Sowell, Ermine Bagby Sowell, and Anne Sowell Margrett, 1939-1954, undated (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Clippings: Taylor Crawford Bagby, Samuel Bagby, Anne Luther Bagby Braly, and Byron Duke Braly, 1959-1966, undated (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Clippings: Helen Bagby Harrison, William Coleman Harrison, Alice Anne Harrison Wise, and Hugh Douglas Wise III, 1919-1977, undated (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Clippings: Albert Ian Bagby, Thelma Firth Bagby, Albert Ian Bagby Jr., Nancy Lee Rogers Bagby and Dan Bagby, 1962, undated (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Clippings: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith: (1 of 2), 1931-1973, undated (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Clippings: Harley Smith and Alice Bagby Smith: (2 of 2), 1931-1973, undated (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Clippings: Helen Frances Smith Hillman, Jimmye Standard Hillman, and Brenda Hillman, 1948-1984, undated (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Clippings: Thelma Lou Smith Cooper and William Frazier Cooper, 1959-1970, undated (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Clippings: Zollie Ruth Voges, William Goodrich Jones, and Doris Goodrich Jones, 1934-1956, undated (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Associacão Antialcoólica and Texas Alcohol Narcotics Education, 1968, undated (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Casa de Correção, 1948-1952, undated (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Clinica Popular Batista Anna Bagby [Medical Clinic], 1949, undated (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Cultural and Civic, 1947-1960, undated (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Clubs and Organizations: English Speaking Club, circa 1942-1967, undated (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Grêmio Náutico União, 1948-1949, 1956, 1967, 1969 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Sociedade Rio Grandense de Educação, 1938, 1941, undated (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Touring Club of Brazil, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Missions: American Baptist Mission of Rio Grande do Sul, 1925-1928 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Missions: Convenção Baptista Estadoal do Rio Grande do Sul, 1925 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Missions: Executive Committee of Southern Baptist Missionaries, 1936, 1939, 1941-1942, 1945 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Missions: Porto Alegre Mission of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1925-1934 (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Missions: South Brazil Mission, 1925, 1946, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Missions: Foreign Mission Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, 1921, 1943-1959, 1972, undated (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Missions: Woman's Missionary Union, 1938, 1944, 1965-1966, 1971, undated (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Clubs and Organizations: Missions: Woman's Missionary Union, 1944, 1954, 1966-1968, undated (Box 103, Folder 27)
    - Programs and Tickets, circa 1913-1968, undated (Box 103, Folder 28)
    - Programs and Tickets, circa 1932-1964, undated (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Programs and Tickets, circa 1940-1966, undated (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Programs and Tickets: Churches, circa 1932-1971, undated (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Calling Cards and Business Cards: (1 of 2), undated (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Calling Cards and Business Cards: (2 of 2), undated (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Guestbook, undated (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Cookbooks and Recipes, circa 1938-1969, undated (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Games, circa 1933-1960, undated (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Music, circa 1927-1930, undated (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Music, circa 1950-1965, undated (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Music: (1 of 3), undated (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Music: (2 of 3), undated (Box 105, Folder 1)